plndr.com 2019-09-17

# Privacy Policy | Plndr.com

This Privacy Policy is intended to inform you about the types of information gathered by Karmaloop, LLC (“we”, “us”) when you use PLNDR.com or the PLNDR mobile app (“PLNDR”), how we use and safeguard that information, and the degree to which you may control the collection and use of that information. We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. If you are a registered PLNDR user, we will attempt to inform you of any material changes by email. Otherwise, you may always view the most recent Privacy Policy on the PLNDR website.

### Information Collection & Use

For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, "personally identifiable information" is any information that identifies you or the device you are using, would enable someone to contact you, or that describes your relationship with PLNDR We collect and store personally identifiable information when you register to use PLNDR, complete a form, conduct a transaction, or send us an email. While you are not required to submit any personally identifiable information to PLNDR, if you do not provide the requested information you may not be able to access or use some of the features and functions of PLNDR and we may not be able to provide you with certain services.

**Orders**

When you place an order, we will request certain personally identifiable information from you on our order form, including your contact information (such as name, email, and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date). We use this information for billing purposes and to fulfill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you. We will securely collect and store all personal financial information you provide to us purposes of processing payments and completing transactions. In some cases we may securely provide this personal financial information to a third party vendor who provides us with payment processing services.

While making a purchase from PLNDR, you are given the option to create a user name and password. This user name and password functionality offers you the ability to quickly and easily proceed through the checkout process on repeat visits.

* * *

 **Surveys or Contests**

PLNDR often provides you the opportunity to participate in contests or surveys on our site. If you participate, we will request certain personally identifiable information from you, including your contact information (such as name and shipping address) and demographic information (such as zip code). We use this information to notify contest winners and award prizes and to send participants our HTML email newsletter. Participation in these surveys or contests is entirely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information.

We may run contests or surveys in conjunction with affiliated websites or services. When we do so, information you provide as part of your contest entry or survey response may also be provided to the affiliated website, but such practices will always be clearly marked at the point of entry.

* * *

 **Tell-A-Friend**

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about PLNDR, we will ask you for your friend’s email address. We will use this email address to send the link to your friend with your personal tracked code to ensure that you can be credited for the referral.

* * *

 **Analytics**

As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We do not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information. We use two third-party tracking services that use cookies to track non-personally identifiable information about visitors.

* * *

 **Cookies**

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We use both session ID cookies and tracking cookies. We use session cookies to make it easier for you to use PLNDR. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. We use tracking cookies to better understand how you use PLNDR, and to enhance your user experience. A tracking cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You are free to decline cookies, but by doing so, you may not be able to take full advantage of all of our offerings. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while using PLNDR.

* * *

 **California Do Not Track Notice**

PLNDR does not track its users over time and across third party websites, and therefore does not respond to Do Not Track signals sent by your browser or mobile application. PLNDR does not authorize the collection by third parties of personally identifiable information from PLNDR users.

### Communications from us

 **Marketing Communications**

As a PLNDR member, you will receive emails from us about products, services, offers, events and promotions, we believe may be of interest to you. We also give members and non-members the option to receive marketing communications from us via SMS messaging to the mobile number you provide to us, and to receive notifications from the Karmaloop mobile app. Out of respect for your privacy, if you no longer wish to receive marketing communications from us, you may opt-out of receiving them as instructed in each email or text message and at www.plndr.com/account/unsubscribe. Be advised, however, that you may not opt-out of receiving communications from us related to technical support or customer service requests, or changes to the PLNDR Terms of Service or Privacy Policy.

You may change the email address and mobile number to which marketing communications will be sent via the My Account section of the PLNDR website or mobile app.

* * *

 **Customer Service Communications**

When you register with PLNDR, we will send you a welcoming email to verify your username and password. We will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide the services you request, and to manage your account. You may elect to receive customer service communications from us via email or telephone.

### Disclosure

We understand how highly our users value the privacy and security of their personally identifiable information. We will disclose information collected from and about you to the following entities for the following purposes: (1) to our related companies, service providers and suppliers, to enable them to fulfill a product or service request or to perform a business, professional or technical support function for us; (2) as necessary if we believe that there has been a violation of our Terms of Service or of our rights or the rights of any third party; and (3) to respond to judicial process and provide information to law enforcement agencies or in connection with an investigation on matters related to public safety, as permitted by law, or otherwise as required by law.

### Third Party Advertisers

PLNDR may elect to display ads from third parties on its website or app properties. The ads appearing on PLNDR are delivered to users by a third party advertising partner. We do not share any website usage information about users with our third party advertising partners.

### Links to Other Sites

PLNDR may contain links to third party websites that are not owned or controlled by us. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such websites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This PLNDR Privacy Policy applies only to information collected by PLNDR.

### Co-branded sites

PLNDR occasionally develops co-branded sites so third parties can re-sell our products through their store or website. The terms of use and privacy policies for each such co-branded site may differ from those of PLNDR. When buying PLNDR products from a co-branded site, please refer to that site’s terms of use and privacy policy.

### Access to Personally Identifiable Information

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, delete or deactivate it by making the change on your My Account page, by emailing our Customer Support at [questions@plndr.com](mailto:questions@plndr.com), or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below

### Security

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If you have any questions about security on PLNDR, you can send email us at [questions@plndr.com](mailto:questions@plndr.com).

### Business Transitions

In the event PLNDR goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred. If you are a registered PLNDR user, you will be notified via email of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information.

### Changes in this Privacy Statement

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you by email and/ or by means of a notice on the PLNDR home page.

### Contact Us

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding this Privacy Policy or any PLNDR product or service, please contact us at:

Email: [questions@plndr.com](mailto:questions@plndr.com)

Last Update: May 16, 2014
